And going from socials to landing page
is going from dance floor to
fingering. Get them a drink first.
So I think that we do need to go through
the stages, because this is the reality.
When I'm messaging a girl on Hinge
and we've matched,
which I don't do because I'm
in a relationship, let's be real.
You both want to fuck or you wouldn't have
matched. You just wouldn't. But there
are stages necessary to go through
before fucking to make sure
that both people are happy that they're
fucking the right person.
Same in business.
If someone's following your page,
I'm not saying everyone
that you're following
wants to fuck you,
but there's some kind of synergy there.
But when someone gets to your email list,
you're close.
You're walking out the club with
that person.
You just got to make sure you don't fuck
it up at this point.
And sometimes it is too much of a leap to
go from socials to landing page.
It is a little bit too much.
It's one drink. Come on, let's go.
They're like, "Whoa, whoa, whoa.
I've just met you." I would say focus on
that
because they might need so many different
points of contact from you before they're
ready to buy,
or they're ready to go to the landing
page, or they're ready to watch
your video.